

Farmingdale, NY

☑ jirka.kopecky@outlook.com | ☑ jirikopecky | Ⅲ jiri-kopecky



Summary_

Software developer at Resideo. 5+ years experience developing server and cloud solutions for connected devices. Nerd who loves to learn about new tools and services, mainly from the .NET world. Out of work loves to play computer games and to read good Sci-Fi or Fantasy book.

Work Experience

Resideo Technologies Inc.

Melville, NY

SENIOR CLOUD SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Sep. 2018 - PRESENT

• Development of core IoT platform

Honeywell - HTS CZ

Brno, Czech Republic

SOFTWARE DESIGN ENGINEER

May 2013 - Aug. 2018

• Co-designed architecture of several IoT Cloud solutions

• Designed and implemented multiple microservices in C# targeting Microsoft Service Fabric

Honeywell - HTS CZ Brno, Czech Republic

TECHNICAL SUPPORT / INTERNSHIP

Apr. 2012 - Apr. 2013

• Support of engineering team that developed IoT services

Blue Pixel Solutions a.s.

Dide Fixet Solutions a.s.

Brno, Czech Republic

C# DEVELOPER / INTERNSHIP

Aug. 2008 - Apr. 2010

• Development of desktop and web applications in C#

Presentation

Microsoft Build 2018 Seattle, WA

Presenter for <How Honeywell migrated their smart thermostat application to Service Fabric>

May 2018

- Summarized how Honeywell Homes Cloud team migrated their solution from Azure Cloud Services to Microsoft Service Fabric
- Available on YouTube: https://youtu.be/VTH2XnMSZ2o

Education ___

Brno University of Technology, Faculty of Information Technology

Brno, Czech Republic

Bachelor of Information Technology

Sep. 2008 - Jun. 2012

Certifications

MICROSOFT EXAMS

- 532: Developing Microsoft Azure Solutions
- 483: Programming in C#

Skills

Programming C#, .NET, .NET Core, PowerShell, TypeScript, JavaScript

Cloud Service Fabric, Microsoft Azure (IoT Hub, Event Hubs, Azure Active Directory)

Microservices Docker, Kubernetes (OpenShift, AKS)

Tools Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, Git

Languages Czech, English

June 23, 2019 Jiri Kopecky · Résumé